    What are biorhythms?                      
Biorhythms are a method to predict three cycles in your life based on your birthday.These cycles are the physical,emotional and intellectual cycle.Each of these cycles goes through different phases: high, low and critical.
    What do the different phases mean? 
If a cycle is above the midline (the 0% line) you experience a high is the corresponding field. If a cycle is below the midline you experience a low and finally if a cycle crosses the midline you experience a critical phase.
If a cycle is in a high phase you are better able to interact in that area. If for example your intellectual cycle is in a high phase you are better able to do exams.
If a cycle is in a low phase it is harder to do well in an area. If for example your emotional cycle is in a low phase you are more irritable.
   What is the meaning of the critical phase?
You experience a critical phase when a cycle crosses the midline. During this time there is a greater risk of errors and accidents.
   Are biorhythms for real?
This is up for you to decide! Just like for example horoscopes and numerology some people believe them and some people don't.
   What's the history of biorhythms?
The scientists Dr. Hermanna Swoboda and Dr. Wilhelm Fliess discovered biorhythms about a hundred years ago. Both scientists weren't working together but discovered biorhythms at about the same time.
   To get help about buttons and other parts of program you can pause on them with your mouse and see the tooltiptext apearing very soon.
   Names and birth dates can be easily saved by pressing Save button.The first name you save will be always the default name. 
   You can use both A.D. Date or solar(persian calender) Date depending on your birth date.
   Keyboard shortcuts can make it easier and faster to work with the plot:pause on the buttons with your mouse to see the same-functioning keys on keyboard.(e.g. R----Refresh,Esc----Exit,Backspace-----------Previous page)
   you can move the plot to future and to past:Just press F to move the plot to future and B to past.⁬⁯⁭                                                                                  